Guide to the East German movie posters, 1968-1974
Department of Special Collections
East German movie posters,
1968-1974
Special Collections M0711
DEFA
6 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Purchased, 1994
Scope and Content
Posters produced by DEFA for films (from many countries including East Germany) which they distributed.
Access terms
Motion picture industry--Germany (East); Motion pictures--Germany (East); Posters
Container List
- Posters for East German Movies (DEFA); Progress Film Vertreib VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 1)
- Posters for East German Movies (DEFA); Progress Film Vertreib VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 2)
- Posters for Movies out of the Soviet - Union; Progress Film Vertreib VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 3)
- Posters for Movies out of the Soviet - Union; Progress Film Vertreib VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 4)
- Posters for West German Movies and West German Coproductions; Posters for Swedish Movies. Progress Film Vertreib VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 5)
- Posters for Polish, Hungarian, and Romanian Movies; Progress Film Vertreib VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 6)
- Posters for Czechoslovakian Movies; Progress Film Vertreib VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 7)
- Posters for Movies out of the USA; Progress Film Vertreib VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 8)
- Posters for French Movies; Progress Film Vertreib VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 9)
- Posters for French-Italian Coproductions; Progress Film Vertreib VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 10)
- Posters for Movies out of Italy, Spain, Denmark and Japan; Progress Film Vertreib VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 11)
- Posters for Movies out England, and various Coproductions; Progress Film Vertreib VEB. [1968-1974] (Box 12)
- Oversized Poster (DEFA) mapcase 4/15